Guide to International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousmen and Helpers of America records: digital edition produced from microfilm, 1904-1952 LAC0004
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Affiliated bodies correspondence and reports, 1907-1952; Series 2; 47 microfilm reels
  - Local unions correspondence, 1907-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1
    - Local #369, Muncie, Indiana, 1949-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 23, Segment 15)
    - Local #370, Deer Lodge, Montana, 1941-1942, 1945, 1947-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 23, Segment 16)
    - Local #371, Rock Island, Illinois, 1941-1945; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 23, Segment 17)
    - Local #371, Rock Island, Illinois, 1946; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 23, Segment 18)
    - Local #371, Rock Island, Illinois, 1947-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 23, Segment 19)
    - Local #372, Detroit, Michigan, 1942, 1946- 1951 /; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 23, Segment 20)
    - Local #373, Fort Smith, Arkansas, 1939, 1942- 1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 23, Segment 21)
    - Local #374, Muskegon, Michigan, 1942-1945, 1949; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 23, Segment 22)
    - Local #375, Buffalo, New York, 1945-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 23, Segment 23)
    - Local #377, Youngstown, Ohio, 1942-1949; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 23, Segment 24)
    - Local #377, Youngstown, Ohio, 1950-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 24, Segment 1)
    - Local #378, Olympia, Washington, 1942-1950; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 24, Segment 2)
    - Local #379, Boston, Massachusetts, 1942-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 24, Segment 3)
    - Local #380, Boston, Massachusetts, 1941-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 24, Segment 4)
    - Local #381, Santa Maria, California, 1944-1948, 1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 24, Segment 5)
    - Local #382, Marion, Illinois, 1942-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 24, Segment 6)
    - Local #383, Sioux City, Iowa, 1940-1945; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 24, Segment 7)
    - Local #383, Sioux City, Iowa, 1946-1947; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 24, Segment 8)
    - Local #383, Sioux City, Iowa, 1948-1949; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 24, Segment 9)
    - Local #383, Sioux City, Iowa, 1950-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 24, Segment 10)
    - Local #384, Norristown, Pennsylvania, 1942, 1944, 1949-; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 24, Segment 11)
    - Local #385, Regina, Saskatchewan, Canada, 1947, 1949, 1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 24, Segment 12)
    - Local #386, Modesto, California, 1942-1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 24, Segment 13)
    - Local #387, Des Moines, Iowa, 1941-1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 24, Segment 14)
    - Local #388, Ottumwa, Iowa, 1940-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 24, Segment 15)
    - Local #389, Los Angeles, California, 1942-1950; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 24, Segment 16)
    - Local #390, Miami, Florida, 1942-1947; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 24, Segment 17)
    - Local #390, Miami, Florida, 1948-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 24, Segment 18)
    - Local #391, Greensboro, North Carolina, 1939, 1942 -1945; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 24, Segment 19)
    - Local #391, Greensboro, North Carolina, 1946-1948; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 24, Segment 20)
    - Local #391, Greensboro, North Carolina, 1949-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 24, Segment 21)
    - Local #392, Cleveland, Ohio, 1942-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 25, Segment 1)
    - Local #393, Beaumont, Texas, 1940-1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 25, Segment 2)
    - Local #394, Carlinville, Illinois, 1943-1945; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 25, Segment 3)
    - Local #394, Des Moines, Iowa, 1946, 1951 -1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 25, Segment 4)
    - Local #395, Moose Jaw, Saskatchewan, Canada, 1943-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 25, Segment 5)
    - Local #396, Kewanee, Illinois, 1942-1943; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 25, Segment 6)
    - Local #396, Los Angeles, California, 1946-1947; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 25, Segment 7)
    - Local #397, Erie, Pennsylvania, 1941-1947; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 25, Segment 8)
    - Local #397, Erie, Pennsylvania, 1948-1950; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 25, Segment 9)
    - Local #397, Erie, Pennsylvania, 1951-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 25, Segment 10)
    - Local #398, Rochester, New York, 1945-1947; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 25, Segment 11)
    - Local #398, Rochester, New York, 1948-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 25, Segment 12)
    - Local #399, Hollywood, California, 1933, 1935, 1941-1944; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 25, Segment 13)
    - Local #399, Hollywood, California, 1945; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 25, Segment 14)
    - Local #399, Hollywood, California, 1946; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 25, Segment 15)
    - Local #399, Hollywood, California, 1947-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 25, Segment 16)
    - Local #400, Cleveland, Ohio, 1940-1942, 1945-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 25, Segment 17)
    - Local #401, Wilkes-Barre, Pennsylvania, 1942-1946; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 25, Segment 18)
    - Local #401, Wilkes-Barre, Pennsylvania, 1947-1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 25, Segment 19)
    - Local #402, Sheffield, Alabama, 1940-1942; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 25, Segment 20)
    - Local #402, Sheffield, Alabama, 1943; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 25, Segment 21)
    - Local #402, Sheffield, Alabama, 1944, Jan. - Aug; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 25, Segment 22)
    - Local #402, Sheffield, Alabama, 1944, Sept., - Dec.; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 26, Segment 1)
    - Local #402, Sheffield, Alabama, 1945-1946; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 26, Segment 2)
    - Local #402, Sheffield, Alabama, 1947-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 26, Segment 3)
    - Local #404, Springfield, Massachusetts, 1917, 1942-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 26, Segment 4)
    - Local #405, St. Louis, Missouri, 1922-1926, 1933; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 26, Segment 5)
    - Local #406, Grand Rapids, Michigan, 1934, 1942- 1946; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 26, Segment 6)
    - Local #406, Grand Rapids, Michigan, 1947-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 26, Segment 7)
    - Local #407, Cleveland, Ohio, 1941-1946; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 26, Segment 8)
    - Local #407, Cleveland, Ohio, 1947-1949; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 26, Segment 9)
    - Local #407, Cleveland, Ohio, 1950; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 26, Segment 10)
    - Local #407, Cleveland, Ohio, 1951-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 26, Segment 11)
    - Local #408, St. Louis, Missouri, 1927-1928, 1943-1946, 1949-1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 26, Segment 12)
    - Local #409, St. Paul, Minnesota, 1940-1944, 1947-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 26, Segment 13)
    - Local #410, Collinsville, Illinois, 1942-1946; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 26, Segment 14)
    - Local #410, Cleveland, Ohio, 1951-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 26, Segment 15)
    - Local #411, Troy, Illinois, 1942, 1944- 1945; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 26, Segment 16)
    - Local #411, Mt. Vernon, Washington, 1947-1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 26, Segment 17)
    - Local #412, Livingston, Montana, 1944-1949, 1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 26, Segment 18)
    - Local #413, Columbus, Ohio, 1942-1944; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 26, Segment 19)
    - Local #413, Columbus, Ohio, 1945-1947; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 26, Segment 20)
    - Local #413, Columbus, Ohio, 1948-1949; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 26, Segment 21)
    - Local #413, Columbus, Ohio, 1950; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 26, Segment 22)
    - Local #413, Columbus, Ohio, 1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 26, Segment 23)
    - Local #413, Columbus, Ohio, 1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 26, Segment 24)
    - Local #414, Fort Wayne, Indiana., 1942-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 27, Segment 1)
    - Local #415, Denison, Texas, 1943-1950; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 27, Segment 2)
    - Local #415, Cornwall, Ontario, Canada, 1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 27, Segment 3)
    - Local #416, Greencastle, Indiana, 1943; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 27, Segment 4)
    - Local #416, El Paso, Texas, 1946-1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 27, Segment 5)
    - Local #417, Vincennes, Indiana, 1939, 1942-1943; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 27, Segment 6)
    - Local #417, Vincennes, Indiana, 1944-1945; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 27, Segment 7)
    - Local #417, Vincennes, Indiana, 1946-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 27, Segment 8)
    - Local #418, Cincinnati, Ohio, 1943-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 27, Segment 9)
    - Local #419, Fresno, California, 1941-1942; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 27, Segment 10)
    - Local #419, Baton Rouge, Louisiana, 1946-1948; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 27, Segment 11)
    - Local #420, Los Angeles, California, 1941-1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 27, Segment 12)
    - Local #421, Dubuque, Iowa, 1941-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 27, Segment 13)
    - Local #422, Cleveland, Ohio, 1945_1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 27, Segment 14)
    - Local #423, Aurora, Illinois, 1940-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 27, Segment 15)
    - Local #424, New York, New York, 1919; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 27, Segment 16)
    - Local #424, Oil City, Pennsylvania, 1942; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 27, Segment 17)
    - Local #424, Oil City, Pennsylvania, 1942; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 27, Segment 18)
    - Local #425, Akron, Ohio, 1942, 1945-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 27, Segment 19)
    - Local #426, Paris, Illinois, 1942-1943; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 27, Segment 20)
    - Local #426, Baltimore, Maryland, 1948-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 27, Segment 21)
    - Local #427, Ketchikan, Alaska, 1946-1950; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 27, Segment 22)
    - Local #428, Steubenville, Ohio, 1943-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 27, Segment 23)
    - Local #429, Reading Pennsylvania, 1939, 1942- .1947; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 27, Segment 24)
    - Local #429, Reading Pennsylvania, 1948-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 27, Segment 25)
    - Local #430, York, Pennsylvania, 1941-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 27, Segment 26)
    - Local #431, Fresno, California, 1940-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 27, Segment 27)
    - Local #432, Oakland, California, 1942-1947, 1950- 1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 27, Segment 28)
    - Local #433, Trenton, New Jersey, 1942, 1946- 1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 27, Segment 29)
    - Local #434, Watertown, Wisconsin, 1941-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 27, Segment 30)
    - Local #435, Denver, Colorado, 1942-1943, 1948- 1949; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 27, Segment 31)
    - Local #436, Cleveland, Ohio, 1942-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 28, Segment 1)
    - Local #437, Haverhill, Massachusetts, 1942-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 28, Segment 2)
    - Local #438, Kankakee, Illinois, 1942-1946; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 28, Segment 3)
    - Local #438, Kankakee, Illinois, 1947-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 28, Segment 4)
    - Local #439, Stockton, California, 1942-1952 /; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 28, Segment 5)
    - Local #440, Columbus, Ohio, 1945-1946; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 28, Segment 6)
    - Local #440, San Francisco, California, 1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 28, Segment 7)
    - Local #441, Bangor, Pennsylvania, 1942-1943; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 28, Segment 8)
    - Local #441, Los Angeles, California, 1948-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 28, Segment 9)
    - Local #442, Madison, Wisconsin, 1941-1948; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 28, Segment 10)
    - Local #442, Madison, Wisconsin, 1949-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 28, Segment 11)
    - Local #443, Bridgeport, Connecticut, 1934, 1941- 1946; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 28, Segment 12)
    - Local #443, Bridgeport, Connecticut, 1947-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 28, Segment 13)
    - Local #444, Columbus, Ohio, 1945-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 28, Segment 14)
    - Local #445, Yonkers, New York, 1940-1946; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 28, Segment 15)
    - Local #445, Yonkers, New York, 1947-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 28, Segment 16)
    - Local #446, Wausau, Wisconsin, 1942-1948; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 28, Segment 17)
    - Local #446, Wausau, Wisconsin, 1949-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 28, Segment 18)
    - Local #447, Denison, Texas, 1941-1944; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 28, Segment 19)
    - Local #447, San Diego, California, 1947; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 28, Segment 20)
    - Local #448, Missoula, Montana, 1942, 1946' -1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 28, Segment 21)
    - Local #449, Cleveland, Ohio, 1921; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 28, Segment 22)
    - Local #449, Buffalo, New York, 1938, 194L -1944; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 28, Segment 23)
    - Local #449, Buffalo, New York, 1945-1948; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 28, Segment 24)
    - Local #449, Buffalo, New York, 1949-1950; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 28, Segment 25)
    - Local #449, Buffalo, New York, 1951-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 28, Segment 26)
    - Local #450, Atlanta, Georgia, 1942-1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 29, Segment 1)
    - Local #451, Cambridge, Ohio, 1942-1947; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 29, Segment 2)
    - Local #451, Seattle, Washington, 1948-1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 29, Segment 3)
    - Local #452, Denver, Colorado, 1942-1947, 1952 1949-; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 29, Segment 4)
    - Local #453, Cumberland, Maryland, 1942-1949 1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 29, Segment 5)
    - skipped, Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 29, Segment 6)
    - Local #453, Cumberland, Maryland, 1950-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 29, Segment 7)
    - Local #454, Springfield, Ohio, 1941-1942, 1946, -1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 29, Segment 8)
    - Local #455, Dixon, Illinois, 1942-1947, 1951-; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 29, Segment 9)
    - Local #456, Yonkers, New York, 1934, 1942-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 29, Segment 10)
    - Local #457, Clinton, Iowa, 1942; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 29, Segment 11)
    - Local #457, Asheville, North Carolina, 1946-1947; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 29, Segment 12)
    - Local #457, Austin, Texas, 1950-1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 29, Segment 13)
    - Local #458, Bluefield, West Virginia, 1943-1945; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 29, Segment 14)
    - Local #458, Detroit, Michigan, 1947-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 29, Segment 15)
    - Local #459, Jersey City, New Jersey, 1942-1946; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 29, Segment 16)
    - Local #459, Jersey City, New Jersey, 1947-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 29, Segment 17)
    - Local #460, St. Joseph, Missouri, 1941-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 29, Segment 18)
    - Local #461, New York, New York, 1932; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 29, Segment 19)
    - Local #461, Tacoma, Washington, 1949-1952 1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 29, Segment 20)
    - Local #462, Peoria, Illinois, 1941-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 29, Segment 21)
    - Local #463, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1934, 1942- 1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 29, Segment 22)
    - Local #464, Vancouver, B. C., Canada, 1943-1949; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 29, Segment 23)
    - Local #465, Seattle, Washington, 1941, 1944- 1945; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 29, Segment 24)
    - Local #466, Jacksonville, Illinois, 1942-1952 1941-; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 29, Segment 25)
    - Local #467, Bernardino, California, 1942-1952 /; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 29, Segment 26)
    - Local #468, Norfolk, Virginia, 1946-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 29, Segment 27)
    - Local #469, Perth Amboy, New Jersey, 1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 29, Segment 28)
    - Local #470, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1914-1915, 1930, • 1945; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 29, Segment 29)
    - Local #470, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1946-1952 -1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 29, Segment 30)
    - Local #471, Minneapolis, Minnesota, 1914, 1941-1943; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 29, Segment 31)
    - Local #471, Minneapolis, Minnesota, 1944-1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 29, Segment 32)
    - Local #472, Seattle, Washington, 1949; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 29, Segment 33)
    - Local #473, Cleveland, Ohio, 1939, 1942, 1947; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Othertype 29, Folder 34)
    - Local #474, Wilmington, Delaware, 1942 1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 29, Segment 35)
    - Local #474, Vacaville, California, 1946; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 29, Segment 36)
    - Local #474, Columbus, Ohio, 1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 29, Segment 37)
    - Local #475, East Liverpool, Ohio, 1942-1943, 1946- 1942-; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 30, Segment 1)
    - Local #476, Massillon, Ohio, 1938, 1942-1945; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 30, Segment 2)
    - Local #476, Buffalo, New York, 1948-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 30, Segment 3)
    - Local #477, Lawrence, Massachusetts, 1943-1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 30, Segment 4)
    - Local #479, New Orleans, Louisiana, 1912-1913, 1917, 1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 30, Segment 5)
    - Local #480, Owosso, Michigan, 1942-1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 30, Segment 6)
    - Local #481, San Diego, California, 1947f 1950; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 30, Segment 7)
    - Local #482, Rockford, Illinois, 1943-1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 30, Segment 8)
    - Local #483, Boise, Idaho, 1942-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 30, Segment 9)
    - Local #484, San Francisco, California, 1942, 1945- -1948; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 30, Segment 10)
    - Local #485, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1942-1947; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 30, Segment 11)
    - Local #485, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1948-1950; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 30, Segment 12)
    - Local #485, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1951-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 30, Segment 13)
    - Local #486, Saginaw, Michigan, 1941-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 30, Segment 14)
    - Local #487, Mankato, Minnesota, 1943-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 30, Segment 15)
    - Local #488, Toronto, Ontario, Canada, 1942, 1947-1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 30, Segment 16)
    - Local #489, Canton, Ohio, 1943-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 30, Segment 17)
    - Local #490, Vallejo, California, 1942-1946, 1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 30, Segment 18)
    - Local #491, Uniontown, Pennsylvania, 1942-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 30, Segment 19)
    - Local #492, Albuquerque, New Mexico, 1941-1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 30, Segment 20)
    - Local #493, New London, Connecticut, 1943-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 30, Segment 21)
    - Local #494, Boston, Massachusetts, 1941-1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 30, Segment 22)
    - Local #495, Los Angeles, California, 1946-1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 30, Segment 23)
    - Local #496, Boston, Massachusetts, 1946-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 30, Segment 24)
    - Local #497, Akron, Ohio, 1942-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 30, Segment 25)
    - Local #498, Kansas City, Kansas, 1939-1944 1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 30, Segment 26)
    - Local #498, Kansas City, Kansas, 1945-1952 1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 31, Segment 1)
    - Local #499, Portland, Oregon, 1946-1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 31, Segment 2)
    - Local #500, Kodiak, Alaska, 1942-1943, 1946-; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 31, Segment 3)
    - Local #501, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1930-1933; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 31, Segment 4)
    - Local #501, Vancouver, Washington, 1942-1943, 1948-; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 31, Segment 5)
    - Local #502, Honolulu, Hawaii, 1947-1950; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 31, Segment 6)
    - Local #503, St. Paul, Minnesota, 1942-1949; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 31, Segment 7)
    - Local #503, St. Paul, Minnesota, 1950-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 31, Segment 8)
    - Local #504, Clinton, Iowa, 1945; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 31, Segment 9)
    - Local #504, Boston, Massachusetts, 1947, 1950- 1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 31, Segment 10)
    - Local #505, Huntington, West Virginia, 1941-1946 -1950; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 31, Segment 11)
    - Local #505, Huntington, West Virginia, 1947-1949 -1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 31, Segment 12)
    - Local #505, Huntington, West Virginia, 1950-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 31, Segment 13)
    - Local #506, Auburn and Geneva, New York, 1941-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 31, Segment 14)
    - Local #507, Green Bay, Wisconsin, 1940, 1943, 1946; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 31, Segment 15)
    - Local #508, Toledo, Ohio, 1942, 1945, 1948; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 31, Segment 16)
    - Local #509, Houston, Texas, 1942-1947; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 31, Segment 17)
    - Local #509, Aiken, South Carolina, 1950-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 31, Segment 18)
    - Local #510, Westwood, California, 1942; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 31, Segment 19)
    - Local #510, Bogalusa, Louisiana, 1948; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 31, Segment 20)
    - Local #510, Omaha, Nebraska, 1951-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 31, Segment 21)
    - Local #511, Kenosha, Wisconsin, 1943, 1949- 1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 31, Segment 22)
    - Local #512, Jacksonville, Florida, 1945-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 31, Segment 23)
    - Local #513, Mattoon, Illinois, 1941-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 31, Segment 24)
    - Local #514, Edmonton, Alberta, Canada, 1943-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 31, Segment 25)
    - Local #515, Chattanooga, Tennessee, 1942-1949; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 31, Segment 26)
    - Local #515, Chattanooga, Tennessee, 1950-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 31, Segment 27)
    - Local #516, Muskogee, Oklahoma, 1941-1952 -1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 31, Segment 28)
    - Local #517, Fresno, California, 1947, 1950- 1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 31, Segment 29)
    - Local #518, West Frankfort, Illinois, 1942-195 2; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 32, Segment 1)
    - Local #519, San Francisco, California, 1942, 1946, 1948-; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 32, Segment 2)
    - Local #520, East Chicago, Indiana, 1941-1949; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 32, Segment 3)
    - Local #520, Moncton, New Brunswick, Canada, 1951-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 32, Segment 4)
    - Local #521, Christopher, Illinois, 1940-1943; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 32, Segment 5)
    - Local #521, Cleveland, Ohio, 1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 32, Segment 6)
    - Local #522, Astoria, Oregon, 1949; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 32, Segment 7)
    - Local #522, Daytona Beach, Florida, 1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 32, Segment 8)
    - Local #523, Tulsa, Oklahoma, 1940; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 32, Segment 9)
    - Local #523, Tulsa, Oklahoma, 1941; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 32, Segment 10)
    - Local #523, Tulsa, Oklahoma, 1942; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 32, Segment 11)
    - Local #523, Tulsa, Oklahoma, 1943; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 32, Segment 12)
    - Local #523, Tulsa, Oklahoma, 1944; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 32, Segment 13)
    - Local #523, Tulsa, Oklahoma, 1945; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 32, Segment 14)
    - Local #523, Tulsa, Oklahoma, 1946; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 32, Segment 15)
    - Local #523, Tulsa, Oklahoma, 1947; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 32, Segment 16)
    - Local #523, Tulsa, Oklahoma, 1948; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 32, Segment 17)
    - Local #523, Tulsa, Oklahoma, 1949; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 32, Segment 18)
    - Local #523, Tulsa, Oklahoma, 1950; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 32, Segment 19)
    - Local #523, Tulsa, Oklahoma, 1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 32, Segment 20)
    - Local #523, Tulsa, Oklahoma, 1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 32, Segment 21)
    - Local #524, Yakima, Washington, 1941-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 32, Segment 22)
    - Local #525, Alton, Illinois, 1942-1946; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 32, Segment 23)
    - Local #525, Alton, Illinois, 1947-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 32, Segment 24)
    - Local #526, Fall River, Massachusetts, 1942-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 32, Segment 25)
    - Local #527, Muskegon, Michigan, 1942-1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Reel 32, Segment 26)